The Fight For Freedom Never Ends
Seal Team Eight: Behind Enemy Lines is a action, war,
drama film directed by Roel Reiné.
Seal Team Eight must fight their way deep into Africa's Congo, decommission a secret uranium mine, and
stop our most dangerous enemy from smuggling weapon's grade yellow-cake out of the country.
Ricks, played by Tom Sizemore.
Lt.Parker, played by Langley Kirkwood.
Officer, played by Bonnie Lee Bouman.
General Ntonga, played by Leroy Gopal.
Case, played by Lex Shrapnel.
Female Tech / Collins, played by Tanya van Graan.
SEAL Team 8: Behind Enemy Lines is a 2014 American action war film
directed by Roel Reiné and starring Tom Sizemore.
It is the fourth installment in the Behind Enemy Lines film series.
The film was released on direct-to-video and Blu-ray on April 1, 2014.
The tone is emotional and thought_provoking.